we were forced to do it That is
мы были вынуждены это сделать То есть
So it's not your
Значит вы не
fault there is a combination of factors a very
виноваты тут совокупность факторов очень
large number of facts
большое количе факто виноват в том что
Russia is to blame for attacking
Россия напала на
Ukraine America is to blame in general
Украину вообще виновата
so
так
Hello from Ukraine the city of Melnitsky
Здравствуйте из украи город мельницкий
Khmelnitsky
Хмельницкий
hni This is between Starokonstantinova and
хни Это между староконстантинова и
Yermolin you are speaking with some strange words
ермолин вы какими-то странными словами
I  from Moscow I understood from
разговариваю Я из Москвы я понял из
Moscow itself or the Moscow region well
самой Москвы или Московской области ну
there is like new Moscow it is in Kiev I
там типа новая Москва это по киевке
understood just something everyone somewhere from the
понял просто что-то все где-то из
Moscow region says that we are from
Московской области говорят что мы из
Moscow I don't know Well Moscow is just
Москвы Я не знаю Ну Москва просто
expanding so I have a Moscow
расширяется вот у меня московская
registration
прописка
that I am from  Moscow Well, I don't know Well,
что я из Москвы Ну я не знаю Ну вот
this is considered as new Moscow,
считается это как новая Москва вас
how many kilometers are you to Moscow according to the
сколько километров до Москвы по
documents, according to the documents, this is Moscow,
документам по документам это Москва вот
but according to the territorial one, this is 7 km
а по если по территориальному это 7 км
from the Moscow Automobile Road. Well, if you consider the Moscow Automobile Road to be
от МКАТ А ну вот если считать МКАТ
Moscow, then I am under Moscow, if you consider the
Москвой то я под московье если считать
Moscow registration, then  I'm from Moscow Well,
прописку Московскую то я из Москвы Ну
it's like villages are joining or there's a
это как вот сёла присоединяются или там
center Well, to the city, like, and already yes, yes, yes There,
центр Ну к городу типа и уже дадада Там
how can I say, Re is really
прям как сказать Ре реально
expanding Was Was  MKAT is
расширяется Была Был МКАТ
now big, I understand, it is already conditionally
сейчас большое понял оно уже условно
like these boundaries are blurred, I understand. And do
типа размывается эти границы понял А
you support the
поддерживаю поддерживаю ли я так
special operation? If you are interested, I can tell you my own. I am interested. I am asking. Yes, that is what it means. Do I support it? Do you think that the special operation is the
считаете ли вы что спецоперация - Это
right action on the part of the
правильное действие со стороны
Russian Federation? And I think so.  that it
Российской Федерации А я считаю что это
couldn't help but
не могло не
happen, you know, that is, everything And since
произойти понимаете то есть всё А с
1914, everything has been heading towards
четырнадцатого года всё шло на пути к
conflict Well, 1914
конфликту Так ну четырнадцатый год это
was already a
уже был
conflict Well, yes, that is, since 1914,
конфликт Ну да ну то есть с четы когда
when Maidan, when about when Maidan,
когда Майдан когда про ког Майдан когда
when you attacked Crimea, captured Crimea
когда вы напали на Крым захватили Крым
Well, that was after the Maidan
Ну так это же было после того как Майдан
started as far as I know No, that was
начался насколько я знаю Нет это было
after you decided to seize Crimea
после того как вы решили захватить Крым
no Maidan Maidan is not Maidan Maidan
нет Майдан Майдан не Майдан майданом
look What does that have to do with it Look there
смотри Какое имеет отношение Вот смотри
was a Maidan elections not elections what
Был Майдан выборы не выборы вот какое
right do you have to seize someone else's country not
вам право захватывать чужую страну не
if
если
you take  if we take
брать если брать
the logic of the Kremlin That is, I don't take I do
логику логику Кремля То есть я не беру я
n't take look I don't take human logic
не беру смотрите я не беру логику
go to you specifically as a citizen  do you
го вас вы конкретно как гражданин
think Russia is acting correctly or
считаете правильно действует Россия или
incorrectly? I can't think Well, that
неправильно А я не могу считать Ну то
is my subjective opinion Yes, as a
есть субъективное моё мнение Да как
subject You are good subjective opinion I
субъект Вы хорошо субъективное мнение Я
think that
считаю что
A Unfortunately we were forced to
А К сожалению мы были вынуждены это
do this That is So it means you are not to blame
сделать То есть Значит вы не виноваты
here there is a very large combination of factors
э тут совокупность факторов очень
Well Who is to blame  Russia is generally to blame for the fact that it
большое Хорошо Кто виноват в том что
attacked
Россия напала на
Ukraine,
Украину вообще виновата
I explain,
объясняю
I explain, because it pursued a
объясняю потому что Она вела
policy of tolerance towards fascism, that is, it
политику толерантности к фашизму то есть
supported, I explain
поддерживала объясняю
[music] it
[музыка]
supported the Nazis, Neo-Nazi
поддерживала нацистов Нео нацистские
organizations, it supported the Nazis in
организации нацистов поддерживала для
order to
того чтобы
[music]
[музыка]
I just had a little drink, it’s
Я просто немножко под выпил
hard,
тяжело
in short, if America had led  itself Well
Короче если бы Америка вела себя Ну
somehow the world Well she can't it's
как-то мир Ну она не может это
capitalism that is capitalism And in Russia it's
капитализм то есть капитализм А в России
not capitalism in Russia well it's like this
не капитализм в России ну он такой
you know in Russia capitalism or not
знаете в России капитализм или не
capitalism capitalism 100% that means
капитализм капитализм 100% то значит
Russia also behaves like a
Россия тоже себя ведёт как
capitalist no here a little here a little here
капиталист нет тут немножко тут немножко
look Here  you said did i understand correctly
смо Вот вы сказали Я правильно понял
that america supporting the nazis
что Америка поддерживая нацистов
forced your russians like
заставила ваших российских типа
melchakov there these dsh rusich to
Мельчакова там вот эти дш Русич так
go to ukraine to the donetsk region
поехать в Украину в донецкую область
fighting against Ukraine is
воевать против Украины
right
правильно
No let's do it this way you know who
Нет давайте так вы знаете кто такой
Milchakov is Well I understand what you're getting at
мильчаков Ну я понял к чему вы ведёте
he's fighting fighting against Ukraine That
ро он воюет воюет против Украины Вот то
is to say it turns out that America
есть получается это его Америка
forced him to fight against Ukraine or
заставила воевать против Украины или
something like that Well he didn't start it No you
как ну не он же это начал Нет ты
Wait that is
Подождите то есть
real  who
реальный который с нацистским флагом
took a photo with a Nazi flag who supported
фоткался который там поддерживал там
animals there and hung out over them specially
животных там вался над ними специально
posted this so he really fights
выкладывал это так вот он реально воюет
for Russia he is now a soldier Well, he is a volunteer
за Россию он сейчас солдат Ну доброволец
and he has a Russian title That is, it
да российское звание имеет То есть
turns out that America forced yours once
получается это Америка заставила ваши
again Wait, let's have some milchaks
ещё раз Подождите давайте мильчаков
now that is, I am right  that America
сейчас то есть я правильно что Америка
forced him to fight against Ukraine
заставила этого воевать против Украины
no So who forced him to fight
нет Так а кто его заставил воевать
against
против
Ukraine Well let's say
Украины Ну давайте так
who it was I have no idea it's probably his
кто его Понятия не имею это его наверное
personal personal choice of a person in Russia everyone
лично личный выбор человека в России все
knows that he is so let's say yes Everyone knows
знают что он так допустим да Все знают
if Russia is fighting against something here
если Россия что-то тут борется против
Nazism in the une how does Russia allow
нацизма в уне то как Россия допускает
that in its composition Yes frank who
что в её составе Да откровенные который
writes Even Ukrainian prisoners do not take
пишет Даже пленных украинцев не брать ть
them and so on about Yary open Yes how is
их и так дальше о Ярый открытый Да как
it if America developed something here
так если Америка что-то развивала тут
therefore Russia is forced  blah-blah-blah
поэтому Россия вынуждена бла-бла-бла
denazification Yes, but in the ranks of the
денацификация Да но в рядах
Russian forces Yes, a huge
российских сил Да воюет огромнейшее
number of
количество
Russians are fighting, what's the joke,
российских в чём же прикол
look I really, I really Well, I have
смотрите Я на самом деле я на самом деле
no right to discuss all this
Ну не в праве это всё обсуждать Потому
Because I simply was not interested in this
что я попросту не интересовался Этой
topic You were probably much
темой Вы наверное интересовались гораздо
more interested  you you so you you were interested you
больше вы вы так вы вы интересовались вы
told me so affirmatively
настолько утвердительно рассказали мне
about America about everything so I
про Америку про всю настолько вот я
understood that you are really interested No I
понял что вы реально интересуетесь Нет я
yes I am interested But at such
да я интересуюсь Но вот в такие
uh at such precise moments I Yeah That is
э в такие точечные моменты я Ага То есть
you just asked somewhere
вы просто поинтересовались где-то
read that it's guilty  America and everything
прочитали что виновата Америка и всё да
and they didn't kill No No No look, each
и не убили Нет Нет Нет смотрите каждого
person has his own way of thinking,
человека есть как бы своё мышление
thinking is made up of information
мышление складывается из информации
that he receives from different sources.
которую он получает из разных источников
I looked at different sources. I
Я смотрел разные источники Я очень
sit there a lot in chat roulette, I
много сижу там в чат-рулетке
periodically
периодически
discuss, I agree with some of your
обсуждаю согласен с некоторыми вашими
statements, but look  there is a fact
утверждениями но смотрите есть есть факт
that how the world works humanity
того что как работает Мир человечество
about fascism about Nazism msya let's say
про фашизм про нацизм мся давайте так
so I named you cha can you name me
вот я вам назвал ча можете мне назвать
some figure like Melkov from the Ukrainians
какую-то фигуру как Мельков из украинцев
Yes which one
Да какого который
you know you passed you
знаеш Вас проходили у вас
passed
проходили
legal e time let's
законные е раз давай е раз
call a specific person wait one more
намри конкретного человека подожди ещ
time specific person Let's do it
раз конкретного человека Давай так
now I'm asking you simple here you
сейчас мне проше пом прост вот ты мне
tell me called Milchakov did you agree did you
скажи назвал мильчаков ты согласился ты
agree tell me in Ukraine in Ukraine
согласился скажи в Украине в Украине
there is some Yary who fights
есть какой-то такой Ярый который воюет
like against Russia, here he is with a
типа против России вот он там с флагом
Nazi flag, you have a
нацистским выступает у вас их очень
lot of them, yes specifically Name them so that I can
много да конкретно Назови их чтобы
sort them out, I checked Maybe I can and I
разобрали я проверил Может дест я и мне
as an ordinary person Why do you say to
как рядовому человеку Зачем п ты говорим
go deeper Wait Stop stop stop you
углубляться Подожди Стоп стоп стоп ты
say that there are a lot of them Name someone
говоришь что их много то Назови кого-то
Why did you decide that there are many of them I don't
С чего ты решил что их много я не
remember
запоминаю
Yes yes yes I understand that is it can't That is
Да да да понял то есть не может То есть
on what basis do you say that there are
вы на основании чего вы говорите что их
many of them name me at least one
много вот назовите мне хотя бы одного
if there are many of them then one I saw I saw a
если их много то од видел я видел очень
lot of proof maybe you can you can now
много доказа може можете можете сейчас
on google at least one We specifically
на гуглите хоть одного Мы конкретно
Nazi marches were in Ukraine let's
нацистские шествия были в укра давайте
now we are about the march now
мы вот сейчас мы про шествие по сейчас
we are with you don't run away I promised now
мы с вами не убегайте я пообещал сейчас
now we are with you about  procession let's
сейчас мы с вами про шествие поговорим
talk now we'll talk yes I'm calling
сейчас мы с вами поговорим да я называю
name me a specific Nazi what are you
назовите мне конкретного нациста что вы
leading away from the topic No look I told you
уводите с темы Нет смотрите я вам сказал
I promise that now we'll talk about
Я обещаю что сейчас мы поговорим про
the procession like this but before that name
шествие ещё так но перед этим назовите
me a specific Nazi from Ukraine I
мне конкретного нациста из Украины Я же
told you I'm not I'm not  I remember the names
сказал Я не я не запоминаю фамилии на
again That is good we have
ещё раз То есть хорошо у нас есть
shows that are supported by the GOK
показов которые поддерживается ГОК
regiment that are supported by the state
полка которые поддерживается государство
Who from the Zov regiment do you put them as
Кто из полка Зов вы их ставите не знаю
your heroes let's do it like this on
своми героями давайте так вот на
Azovstali so here's the past
азовстали так вот былом
f there is this let's do it like this Here's Kalina so for
ф есть это давайте так Вот калына так
example here are those that  were eh on
например вот те которые были э на
Azovstal Here
азовстале Вот
he is I have no idea by last names I
он я понятия не имею по фамилиям я по
don't remember by last names
фамилиям не
you are in one you are in one Who of you
запоминаю вы в одну вы в одну Кто из
look well you know who is the main one in
смотрите хорошо знаете кто главный
Ukraine who is Zelensky oh I knew that you would say that
Украине кто Зеленский о Я так и знал что
this Jew you are going to say that he is
вот этого еврея вы сеча скажете что он
super awesome
супер обалденно
he is  because here I am
он потому что вот я
I very much I was for a huge time well let's
Я очень я огромное время был ну
say I explain I will now lead to
скажем я объясняю я сейчас подведу к
this
этому
And at the beginning Zelensky says I
А по началу Зеленский говорит я
talk  in Russian it is
разговариваю на русском языке это для
my native language I will never
меня родной язык Я никогда не буду
speak another language so Okay there is
говорить на другом языке так О'кей есть
such a fact he
такой факт он это
said this at the beginning at the beginning of the reign
говорил в начале в начале правления
literally 2 weeks pass I was
проходит буквально 2-т недели я был
subscribed to his
подписан на его Так
So 2-3
и проходит 2-3
weeks pass changes  rhetoric absolutely in the
недели меняет риторику абсолютно в
opposite direction that that this is how a
противоположную сторону что что так
person acts Well so so Independent
человек поступает Ну так так Независимый
person help let's look Putin
человек помо давайте так смотрите Путин
said that they will not raise the retirement
говорил что не не поднимут пенсионный
age raised he says that there was no will not
возраст поднял он говорит что не было не
be mobilization did mobilization this is how a
будет мобилизации сделал мобилизацию так
person acts People tend to
человек поступает Людям свойственно
change some of their own a person acts
менять какие-то свои человек поступает
situationally wait situationally what
ситуативно подожди ситуативно то в чём
situation
ситуация
not he started speaking exclusively
не он стал разговаривать исключительно
in
на украинском
Ukrainian I too it turns out I
языке Я тоже я получается я 20 лет назад
started speaking completely in
полностью начал разговаривать на
Ukrainian 20 years ago I became this moment
украинском языке я стал вот этот момент
when I became I understood everyone who I am Understand
когда я стал я понял все кто я Поня
Wait wait again That is  you
Подожди подожди ещё раз То есть ты
claim that the person started
утверждаешь что человек стал
speaking completely in
разговаривать полностью на украинском
Ukrainian, which means he was influenced by it, wait
языке значит он на него повлияли подожди
again,
ещё раз
fact, you said that it was because he
фак ты сказал что он из-за того что он
switched to Ukrainian, yes, and
перешёл на украинский язык так да А
why, what
почему че него
influenced him  In what why are you talking about it?
повлияло В чём с чего ты говоришь пов
Look, it’s because he started
Вот смотри он из-за того что он начал
speaking
говорить
Ukrainian because of how it is about
по-украински изза того как это прои о
Poli if he starts speaking English in 2 weeks
Поли е если он за 2 недели начнёт
he
говорить по-английски он
will be And what does this have to do with it? I’m saying the fact. I’m
будет А при чём тут это я говорю факт
saying  fact yes you said fact look the
говорю факт да ты сказал факт смотри
scary fact that the president of Ukraine
страшный факт что президент Украины
said that
говорил что
he he began to live he became president and
онм он стал пожить он стал президентом и
began to speak Ukrainian in short in
стал короче говорить по-украински через
2 weeks and if he had
2 недели а если бы он через 2 недели
started speaking English in 2 weeks he would also have
начал по-английски говорить он тоже бы
been a nast that's how it is  a person so a
был настом вот так так человек так
politician does not change his еще чем мне мне мне мне мне мне мне мне мне мне мне мне мне мне мне мне мне мне мне мне мне мне мне мне мне мне мне мне мне мне мне мне
политик не меняет сво ещ раз смотри вот
about the
знаю сказал про я Дава не давай мы про
language of yours  if he had started speaking Hebrew in a few weeks,
язык тево если он начал бы через недели
he would have
говорить на иврите он был
been And I said the fact, I explain the fact,
бы Причём я сказал факт объясняю фак
he became president, he began speaking
было он стал президентом начал говорить
Ukrainian If he had become president, he
по-украински если бы он стал президентом
began speaking Hebrew, he would
начал говорить на иврите он стал
have become  I guess I don't
бы Наверно я не
know logic I explain my logic as a
знаю логика я объясняю свою логику какр
citizen of an ordinary person I'm not I'm not a
гражданин рядового человека я не я не
politician I'm not a blogger I'm who I am
политик я не блогер я кто я
just let's do it this way if I form my opinion
просто давай так если ра своё мнение
I form my opinion from
составляю я своё мнение составляю из
logic from the logic of what's happening What is
логики из логи происходящего Что такое
Nazism let's figure it out this way What is
нацизм давай так разберёмся Что такое
Nazism  Nazism - This is when you put
нацизм нацизм - Это когда ты ставишь
your nation above all others. Understand
свою нацию превыше всех остальных понял
where in this phrase the other nations are.
где в этой фразе остальные нации
Let's say, yes, if this is Nazism, then in the World Cup, then the problem is for the president of Ukraine to speak Ukrainian. Well, let's follow the
Украины Ну давайте проследим риторику
president's rhetoric. Tell me again what Nazism is.
президента ещ раз скажите что такое
Repeat When.  your
Повторите Когда твоя
nation is above all others and there and you
нация превыше всех остальных и там и
want
хотите
others here prezi state ukraine
других вотт прези государство
official language state language
укра официальным языком государственным
is ukrainian Yes I explain its
есть украинский Да я объясняю его
transformation well What does it have to do with it look I
трансформацию ну Причём тут смотрите я
asked what is nazism If you
спросили что такое нацизм Если вы ещё
look again if you said that nazism
раз смотри если бы вы сказали что нацизм
is when a person is over 2  weeks undergoing
- это когда человек за 2 недели проходит
transformation from Russian Russian
трансформацию от российского русского
language to Ukrainian this is Nazism we
языка до украинского это нацизм мы тогда
could then discuss it with look
бы это могли обсуждать с смотрите
let's go let's go  so let's give another
давайте давайте так Давайте ещё одну
analogy that is very suitable for this.
аналогию очень подходящую к этому Вот
Look, you are a person. Have
смотрите Вы человек
you ever
вы когда-нибудь
lied? Of course, everyone has lied. Yes, everyone
врали да Конечно каждый врал Да каждый
has lied. Have you ever. Look,
врал вы когда-нибудь вот смотрите
for example, you lie to one
например вы врёте одному
person. Two
человеку проходят 2
weeks pass and you change your rhetoric. That
недели и вы меняете свою риторику то
means I am not worth it.  it's not you who change your
значит я стою не не вы меняете свою
rhetoric you will do it like a
риторику вы будете так делать как
person it happened every time you live like a
человек бывало бывало каждого жи как
reasonable person VM your memory
разумным ВМ у вас память
works remember what happened 2 weeks
работает помните что было 2 недели
ago Look for example 2 weeks ago I
назад Смотри я например 2 недели назад
said that I won't be for example in chat
сказал что я не буду например в чат
roulette Yes after 2 weeks I started  cover
рулетке Да через 2 недели я начал крыть
everyone I stand from this
всех я от этого
No you become a person
стою Нет вы становитесь человеком
who How to say changed his mind
который Как сказать изменил сво мнение
Change No you did not change your mind you are
Измени Нет не изменили сво мнение вы
irrational and
нерационально и
inconsistent
непоследовательно
consistent then if you say that there
последователь то если вы скажете что там
Zelensky Inconsistent in his
Зеленский Не последовательны в свои
actions this can be discussed Yes What does the
действиях это можно обсуждать Да Причём
Nazi have to do with it T the question is
здесь наци Т вопрос
why why  he is not a follower of this
почему почему он не последователь это че
phenomenal
феноменальной
pa days after his inauguration
па через дня после его инаугурации
aliens arrived and said and aliens are
инопланетяне и сказали а инопланетяне -
this  The heirs of the ancients s drank themselves to death
это Наследники древних у с ску спился
Ukraine Well, that's how it was like a friend Well, it was
Украин Ну так и было как подруго Ну тоже
n't the Nazis who came to him and said those
не нацисты к нему пришли и сказали те
aliens Well, that means he's an alien, that
инопланетяне Ну значит он инопланетяни
means he's an alien That means
значит он инопланетян То есть получается
aliens Yes, they influenced him to
инопланетяне Да повлияли на него чтобы
speak Ukrainian and he became an
он разговаривал украинской и он стал
alien power Was Was
инопланетянином власть Была Был
Poroshenko, come on, wait, let's
Порошенко давай Подожди п Давай мы с
finish with Zelensky one more time. You're stealing the te
Зеленским закончим ещ раз Ты спр те те
e. No, let's do it this way so that we can
е Нет давай так чтобы мы тебя
mess around with you in Russian. And after 2 weeks he
повозиться по-русски А через 2 недели
started speaking Ukrainian. Yes, he's
начал говорить по-украински Да он
not a politician, you're a politician, you
политики так не поступают ты ска
're not a politician, this is his
политики не поступает это его
political question.  Well, if you
политический вопрос Да вот если ты
say politicians don't act like that, such
говоришь политики так не поступают такие
What is Nazism popa Well, except for
В чём нацизм поупа Ну кроме кроме
Lukashenko, yes What is Nazism Let's be
Лукашенко да В чём нацизм Давайте будем
OTK That is, if a politician said something
ОТК То есть если политик что-то говорил
and didn't keep his word, he started doing it
а не сдержал своё слово там начал
differently, he's a bad politician, what is he? And
по-другому дест плохой политик ч он А
Nazism  what does it have to do with it Well, given that he
нацизм при чём Ну при том что на него
was influenced by who benefits, go ahead, who
повлияли кому выгодно подите кому
benefits  you said that Zelensky is a Nazi
выгодно ты сказал что Зеленский нацист
who benefits from the president
кому выгодно чтобы президент
speaking exclusively in Ukrainian to
разговаривал исключительно на украинском
people from Ukraine because well, we don't have Ukrainian as the
людям из Украины потому что ну у нас не
state language for people from Ukraine, we have
людям из Украины государственный язык у
Ukrainian, you don't have
нас украинский у вас у вас не
Ukrainian as the state language, your
государственный язык украинский у вас
state language is Ukrainian and
государственный язык украинский и
Russian Open the Constitution where we have
русский Открой Конституцию где у нас
Russian has never been an official language, what did you change the constitution for?
русский что вы там меняли конституцию бы
Show me where in the constitution it was that
Покажи мне где в Конституции было что
Russian was the official language, at least
руский язык государственный хоть
once show me there were no other languages.
когда-то покажи было иных языков не было
We never had two official
у нас никогда два государственных
languages. What do you mean there were no languages. All of
языка было что значит не было увас вся
Ukraine spoke Russian.
Украина разговаривала на русском языке
ro deep reserve and now they say
ро глубокого запас и сейчас говорят
look come on come on you Chechnya
смотри давай так давай так у вас Чечня
speaks
разговаривает на
Chechen Yes Chechen is your second
чеченском Да чеченский у вас второй
state language they probably do yes no
государственный у них наверно да нет у
you Chechen is your second state language or
вас чеченский второй государственный или
not They probably do yes
нет У них наверно да
no you you have one state
нет у вас у вас один государственный
language and we have  one state language
язык и у нас один государственный язык
yes then with two state languages
да то при два государственных языка
find come on so look you I finally
найди давай так смотри ты я окончательно
call you come on find me now
называю тебя давай находишь мне сейчас
when in the Constitution there were two in the
когда в Конституции было два в
Constitution there are two state
Конституции записано два государственных
languages ​​and I publicly
языка и я публично
apologize Come on  come on find me in which
извиняюсь Давай давай найди мне в какой
article of the Constitution there were two
статье Конституции было два
state languages ​​in our country and when
государственных языка у нас и когда
I'll also look maybe I'll
Я тоже поищу може Я
shorten it up
короче
let's say the Constitution of
давай так конституция
Ukraine 978 But
Украины 978 Но
first what year are you
первы какой ты год
taking Well starting from seventy eighth
берёшь Ну начиная с семьдесят восьмого
where is the Soviet Union still with us
де поди это Советский Союз ещё был у нас
it was adopted
она принята
where is the
де
new one  The Constitution of Ukraine was adopted In the
новая Конституция Украины принята В
ninety-sixth year before that the
девяносто шестом году до этого ещё
Soviet was still in force urs Well, now we
Советская действовало урс Ну мы сейчас
will trace the entire history of your
проследим всю всю историю вашей
Constitution so citizenship of Ukraine so
Конституции так гражданство Украины так
basic rights and
основные права и
freedoms
свободы
Open the Constitution of Ukraine article
Открывайте Конституцию Украины статья
Surrender Do you
Отдайся
want me to read it to you so that you don't
Хочешь я тебе зачитаю чтобы ты долго не
have to search for a long time You can read as much as you want I
искал Ты может читать сколько угодно я
I will be my sources
буду своим источникам
Dava Secret
Дава Тайный
source Where was it in our Constitution that there
источник Где же там у нас в Конституции
were two languages ​​from me they
было два языка от меня что-то
hid something When I was studying law
скрывали Я когда учился на юридическом
these teachers did not tell me the whole Constitution
эти преподы мне не всю Конституцию
and
рассказали и
to add salt on the Internet falsified
подсолить в интернете фальсифицированные
probably here now you have a source that
наверное вот у вас сейчас источник
will turn all my knowledge about  Ukrainian
перевернёт всё моё познание о Украинской
Constitution Oh my God I hope he doesn't
Конституции Ой блин Боже Хоть бы он не
find anything about the Russian language in the Constitution that
нашёл про русский язык в Конституции что
we have  state this is me so oh
у нас то государствен это же я так о
shame oh god oh god man no no Find
позор боже боже боже мужик не не Найди
please don't find I don't want to
пожалуйста не найди Я не хочу
disgrace myself in front of people
опозориться перед людьми
Help And how much by the way Stream
Помогите А сколько кстати Стрим
4800 Normal Normal this is all
4800 Нормально Нормально это сейчас все
you will show there article ten there and there it
вы покажете там статья десятая там и там
says Russian
написано русский
language
язык Вот
This is just brutal and  everyone will write fu
это просто жесть и все будут писать фу
pop in short damn juris
поп короче блин юрис
You are looking for I will call Hello give me Stefanchuk
Вы ищете я позвоню Алло дайте стефанчука
please there you can please on the site
ласка там можете будь ласка на сайте
Supreme for now Ternovo edit
верховно ради зараз терново редагувати
the Constitution so that there are no nasty things about the fact
Конституцию щоб там не було гадок про те
that Russian language is another state because here I am now
що россий мова другою державною бо тут я
watching roulettes zap all type  what will
сечас вчать рулетки запа вся типк что
you find in short me such a disgrace will be Well I don't
найде короче ме такий позор буде Ну не
want Khmelnitsky to be disgraced you know
хоче чтоб Хмельницкий посрав знаете
Stefanchuk was also like [ __ ] from
стефанчук тоже був типа Даго з
Khmelnitsky yes All got home and then
Хмельницкого да Всё домовились да потим
return PS roulette here PS 12 years
вернете ПС рулетки десь ПС 12 години
you can  I'll return it back now learn
можете верну назад зараз выучить Угу
Ugu Okay, that's it, come on, you'll find everything, Tanechka And
О'кей всё давай ты всё ви Танечку А
now you definitely won't find it I'm so
теперь точно не найдёшь Я до позарился
greedy, the head of the Verkhovna Rada from
руть глава Верховной Рады из
Khmelnitsky is also a
Хмельницкого родо тоже
lawyer, I had to look faster, already
юрист надо было быстрее искать уже
deletes, deletes
удаляет удаляет
in the evening, return But after our
вечером вернуть Но уже после нашего
conversation, lo izna Ruslanom  once yes everything
разговора ло изна Русланом раз да всё
in short thank you BN it's really so cool
короче дякую БН реально так прикольно
in short dude for looking for something it's already been seen
короче чувак за шукае шка воно видалено
no more remember you'll be amazed go and have a look
нема пом подивишся зайде вдо глянеш
in short Like handsome young so we'll keep it
короче Лайко красавчики моло так и будем
hot What do you have there Yak
х жари Что там у вас Як
right
спра норм
ok Everything is not in the order come on
Да окей Всё не вка давай
[music]
[музыка]
what-  then my interlocutor's confidence disappeared
что-то пропало уверенность у моего
where is that daring
собеседника где этот дерзкий
ardor where is that steel in the eyes
пыл где это сталь в глазах
And I already see sadness sadness Your eyes
А я уже вижу печаль печаль Ваши глаза
They are wandering around the Internet somewhere but
Они где-то так бродят по интернету но в
sadness is felt in them Here in the Ukrainian
них чувствуется печаль Вот в украинском
language the word tuga here I see such tuga and
языке слово туга вот я бачу такую тугу и
bente in  in your
бенте в ваших
eyes I love these moments  emotional
очах Я люблю эти моменты эмоционального
pleasure I know I'm like a vampire I
наслаждения я знаете я как вампир
suck out all the life energy from
вытягиваю все жизненные энергии вот из
people that they are looking for sadly
людей которые они вот так ищут печально
and can't find I just feel my You
и не могут найти Я просто ощущаю свою
know there's something in this sk I start to
Знаете что-то есть в этом ске Я начинаю
feel some kind of superiority even
ощущать какой-то свой превосходство даже
you
вы
understand that
понимаете что вот
uh  a man searches and searches and now he can't
ээ человек ищет ищет и теперь не может
find what he so ardently said that
найти то что он так яро рассказывал что
yes, it exists and I'm a
да это есть а я тут
liar here it's just heavenly pleasure
брехун это просто Райское наслаждение
you know, you can sit like this,
знаете вот можно так сидеть вот это звук
listen to this clicking sound and just olde it's
клацают слушать и вот просто олде это
like you know, firewood in the fireplace crackles like
как знаете дрова в камине трещат по
crackling You  so you sit there,
трески Ты так сидишь
swing and think Is there
качаешься и думаешь
life on other planets And
А есть ли жизнь на других планетах А
if they are aliens, are they Ukrainians or not
если е инопланетяне они украинцы или нет
What language do they
На каком языке они
speak Can you voice what you are
говорят А можете озвучить что вы сейчас
watching now I am interested in where your
смотрите вот мне интересно ж куда ваша
inquisitive mind has led you Where have you been
пытливый ум вас завёл Где же вы так
looking for an article for so long  Constitutions about the
долго ищете статью в Конституции про
Russian language the
русский язык
processor
процессор
overheated Let me give you one
перегрелся Давайте я вам Даю одну минуту
more minute to
ещё на
search now the timer is right the timer I
поиск сейчас таймер прям таймер так
will do it like
сделаю
this the
так
timer we turn on one minute minut Start
таймер включаем одну минуту minut Старт
no Yes
не Да
start now it  beep How will
старт сейчас он запикать Как
such a song end in the Soviet Union there
закончит такая песня в Советском Союзе
was
была
Hope my
Надежда мой компас
earthly compass here you have another you have
земной вот у вас есть ещ вы так взгляд
changed your view It seems so here it is this
изменили Вроде так вот она это
article that you sent me
статья что вы скинули мне
Read Well Read that Java
Прочитайте Ну Прочитайте что Ява
sent everything timer
скинул всё таймер
[music]
[музыка]
cool sound of the timer on the
прикольный звук у таймера на
phone Well  what we are stating that howled
телефоне Ну что мы констатируем что выл
or will you take an extra minute that's
или возьмёте дополнительную минуту
it dude come on I understand that you want to
всё чувак давай я понимаю что ты хочешь
merge He will sit like this for another 4 days
слиться Он ещё 4 дня буде так сидить
[music]
[музыка]
for And so he talked talked in short a lot
за А так базарил базарил короче багато
what there
что там
was even something to say
навали даже чего сказа
Let me just please write Put
Дайте я просто пож по пишиться Поставьте
a like on  channel I just I adore those
лайк на канал Я просто я обожнюю та
moments so ko vva so povnu donation
моменты так ко вва таку повну донацию
so in short already like you know VN sit
так короче вже типа знаете ВН сиди
like that now
такий сечас
yay ivto
яй ивто
need I'll throw VN vzh tru famous such
треба закину ВН вж тру знатен такий
internal mop b robit VS who to get
внутрення швабра б робить ВС хто отримав
emotions  aesthetic satisfaction from this
эмоций естетичне задоволення з цього
video is written to the channel put a like
ролика пишиться на канал поставте лайк
write to Telegram in the description P video about
пишиться на Telegram в опис П видео о
So we are their Press Glory to
Так мы их Жам Слава
Ukraine write to Telegram right now
Украине пись на й Telegram прям зараз
axis VN and
ось ВН а
pok ce very and very important YouTube is busy
пок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
through scarg or in your ban and very  I do
на через скарг ор в твый бан и дуже
n't show a lot of videos to people sometimes I don't
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams That's
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
why I write the latest news
того щоб ми Мали оперативний звязок
right now and while there's
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
still interesting and useful information in Telegram and OKM videos
окм видео ще теж цикава и корисна
and we'll show you the
информация и мы повинни з вами трима
latest news independently
постийний оперативный звязок незалежно
in order to show you  about this YouTube
в того чи покаже вам про це YouTube
Glory to Ukraine subscribe
Слава Украине подпишись